

RAFAAHA YOUSUF

ASSISTANT MANAGER DESIGN

About Me

I am Highly experienced, creative, and well-versed in design aesthetic experienced Brand Designer specialized in Branding, website, marketing multimedia, video editing, motion graphics and print design. Exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills; very strong team player with well-developed written, verbal and management abilities.

Contact

Phone | +92 346 2810863

Email | muhammedrafaaha@gmail.com

LinkedIn | https://bit.ly/3TlOgrj

Behance | https://bit.ly/3CJlhqi

Vimeo | https://bit.ly/3VvBI0U

Technical Skills

- Video Editing
- Typography
- Brand Identity
- Social Media Posts
- UI/UX Design
- Print Design
- Videography
- Illustration

Work Experience

Utopia Industries | Karachi, Pakistan August 2023 - Present

Assistant Manager Design

- Developing Amazon Listings, Store Pages, Amazon EBC, and etc.
- Creating and managing the company's visual brand identity.
- Produce engaging motion graphics including, promos, Facebook ads, Instagram posts, and animated banners.
- oversees the creation and execution of design solutions including imagery, charts, Infographics, and multimedia elements used for marketing, advertising, and sales.
- Ensure final graphics and layouts are visually appealing and represent the best brand image.

KoderLabs | Karachi, Pakistan March 2020- August 2023

Graphic Designer

- Managed all design projects from concept to delivery.
- Ensured brand consistency throughout various marketing projects.
- Conceptualized original website design ideas that brought simplicity.
- Designed artwork of brochures, print, posters, digital displays, flyers, presentations. and other publications based on individual client requirements.

Salsoft Technologies | Karachi, Pakistan Apr 2018 - Feb 2020

Graphic Designer Executive

- Collaborated with the creative director and graphic design manager to develop design concepts.
- Designed LinkedIn/Twitter/Facebook posts.
- Prepared rough drafts and presented ideas; amended designs after feedback.
- Editing video footage, adding effects/elements, and doing color grading to enhance motion graphics.

Software Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe AfterEffect
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Zeplin
- Overflow.io

Achievements

- Goal Setting Workshop | 2014
- 13th YLC Conference | 2014
- Aptech Ambassador | 2015
- Student Of the Year | 2016

References

Muhammad Umair

Senior Graphic Designer 03122021918 | muhammad.umair@Koderlabs.com

"He is young, obedient, enthusiastic and hardworking fellow and capable of discharging duties entrusted to this diligently. He has a pleasing personality, well-behaved and punctual to the best of our knowledge, so also bears good moral character."

AUBAID ASHRAFI

Motion Graphic Specialist
0322 1369149 | Aubaidashrafi@koderlabs.com

"Mr. Rafaaha was an active member of the KoderLabs team and supported colleagues professionally and personally. I'd like to express my strong support for Mr. Rafaaha's application. Mr. Rafaaha is a self-confident, proactively helpful, smart, creative and punctual leader. I recommend Mr. Rafaaha without any reservation."

Education

Advance Diploma in MultiMedia

2015 - 2018

Arena MultiMedia

Bachelor of Design

2014 - 2018

Karachi University

Graphic Design Certification

2014

Zas College (BBSYDP)

Certifications

Principle of Design

LinkedIn Learning | 2020

Style Guides and Design Systems

LinkedIn Learning | 2019

Design Thinking Process

LinkedIn Learning | 2019